♪ I'm going down to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Going down to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting "howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ Headed on up to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park ♪
♪ And meet some friends of mine ♪
South.Park.S11E03.Lice.Capades
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@ID Sync:FRM@mablelee
双语合成 Lv&daisy
好啦 孩子们 快坐好吧
ALRIGHT, STUDENTS, LET'S TAKE OUR SEATS.
学校今天有个小问题
APPARENTLY, WE HAVE A LITTLE PROBLEM HERE AT THE SCHOOL
要和大家一起商量解决
WHICH WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT.
我知道啦！
AH, YES,
是关于那些犹太人的事吧
YOU MEAN THE JEW PROBLEM.
学校当局终于要采取措施了 我很欣慰啊
GOOD, GOOD, I'M GLAD WE'RE FINALLY GOING TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
没啊 我说的是关于头虱的事
NO, I MEAN THE PROBLEM OF HEAD LICE.
不久前丹佛有所学校 有过一次虱子大爆发
THERE'S BEEN A LICE BREAKOUT AT A SCHOOL IN DENVER
所以我们学校也要防患于未然
AND WE NEED TO MAKE SURE NOBODY SPREADS IT HERE.
我们班上有人有头虱？
SOMEBODY MIGHT HAVE LICE?!
所以今天 大家都得去学校体育馆里
SO TODAY YOU ARE ALL GOING TO THE GYMNASIUM
好好的检查一下
TO HAVE YOUR SCALPS EXAMINED.
这没什么必要吧
THAT IS COMPLETELY UNNECESSARY.
大家都知道 只要穷人身上才会长虱子
EVERYONE KNOWS THAT ONLY POOR PEOPLE CAN GET LICE.
所以只要检查Kenny就好了嘛
THE ONLY ONE THAT COULD SPREAD IT HERE IS KENNY.
虾米?!
WHAT?!
我操!
F YOU!
我个人也觉得我们班没什么问题
I'M SURE THIS CLASS IS CLEAN,
但最好还是检查一下
BUT WE'RE GOING TO BE EXAMINED
这样就算有人真的得了虱子
SO THAT IF ANYONE HAS THE LICE
学校也好在其传播前采取措施
WE CAN STOP IT BEFORE IT SPREADS.
每个人的头发里都可能有头虱
LICE CAN LIVE IN ANYBODY'S HAIR.
哈罗 Kelly.
HELLO, KELLY.
宝贝今天还好吗？
HOW'S MY BABY?
你是说我呢？ 还是说我们的小宝宝？
YOU MEAN ME, OR THE LITTLE ONE?
当然是你们两个一起啦
I MEAN BOTH.
嗯 除了在等你回家时有一些孤独
WELL, BESIDES A LITTLE LONELINESS WAITING FOR DADDY TO COME HOME,
我想我们都还好拉
I GUESS WE'RE BOTH OKAY.
我是如此幸运 能和你这么美丽的虱子结合
HOW DID A LOUSE LIKE ME GET SO LUCKY TO HAVE A LOUSE LIKE YOU?
这才不是什么幸运呢 Travis
LUCK HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IT, TRAVIS.
大家加油啊！ 好样的!
-LICE GET ER DOWN! -THAT'S IT! -GOOD!
你没事吧?
YOU OKAY?
有时候
SOMETIMES
我有些担心我们宝宝出生后 的成长环境
I JUST WORRY WHAT KIND OF WORLD OUR BABY IS GOING TO GROW UP IN.
我还是再回丛林一趟
I NEED TO RUN OUT TO THE FOREST
再研究分析一下好了
AND DO ANOTHER SEDIMENT ANALYSIS.
我觉得我们似乎对这片土地 索取得太多了
I'M WORRIED WE MIGHT BE OVERWORKING THE TERTIARY LAYER.
所有学生都按照年级的顺序排好队
ALL STUDENTS MAKE SURE YOU ARE IN LINE ACCORDING TO YOUR GRADE.
当轮到你们检查的时候
WHEN YOU REACH THE FRONT OF THE LINE,
你们就要进入幕布后面 把帽子脱下来好好检查
YOU WILL GO BEHIND THE CURTAIN AND REMOVE ANY HATS TO BE CHECKED.
天哪 我真希望他们在我身上 找不出虱子
BOY, I SURE HOPE THEY DON'T FIND LICE IN MY HAIR!
你知道你如果被检查出有虱子 会是什么后果吗？
WHAT DO YOU THINK HAPPENS IF YOU DO HAVE IT?
他们会把你拖出去
THEY DRAG YOU OUT OF HERE,
把你丢进一个大厕所里面
PUT YOU IN THIS BIG CONTAINMENT FACILITY,
然后他们就会把一根插满果酱的铁棍子 狠狠地插进你的小屁眼
WHERE THEY STICK A COLD METAL PIPE UP YOUR ASS WITH THIS CLEAR JELLY
然后再把你的小蛋蛋捏碎
AND THEN THEY SHOCK YOUR BALLS.
我是干净的!
I'M CLEAN!
我就知道我才不会有什么臭头虱
I KNEW I DIDN'T HAVE ANY STUPID HEAD LICE!
这根本就没什么意义嘛
THIS IS RIDICULOUS,
其实我们所有人都只不过是来 来陪Kenny检查而已
ALL THIS JUST SO THEY CAN SEND KENNY AND HIS STUPID HEAD LICE HOME.
贱人 日你！
DUDE! ???
在椅子上坐好
HAVE A SEAT ON THE STOOL.
噢 噢 看来你有头虱哦！
OH, OH... LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT 'EM.
什么?!
WHAT?!
你有头虱
YOU HAVE LICE.
你叫Clyde Harris 没错吧？
LET'S SEE...CLYDE HARRIS, IS IT?
噢 天啊!!!
OH, MY GOD!!!
耶稣你怎么这样对我!
OH, CHRIST NO!
别紧张嘛 这没什么大不了的
NOW, NOW... IT'S ALRIGHT.
我们只需要打个电话给你家长
WE'RE GOING TO CALL YOUR PARENTS
让他们带你去看医生就好了
AND GET YOU TO YOUR DOCTOR.
你根本就不知道事态的严重性！
PLEASE, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
对其他孩子来说 我会成为永远的头虱笑料的
THE OTHER KIDS ARE GONNA MAKE FUN OF ME FOREVER!
你的朋友们没有那么贱吧？
I'M SURE YOUR FRIENDS AREN'T THAT CRUEL.
他们就那么贱!
YES! THEY ARE!
总统先生!
MR. PRESIDENT!
总统先生 大事不好啦!
MR. PRESIDENT, I BELIEVE WE HAVE A SERIOUS PROBLEM!
环境正在发生剧变
THE ENVIRONMENT IS CHANGING.
我想这也许是我们的过度开发而造成的
I BELIEVE IT IS SOMEHOW REACTING TO OUR PRESENCE ON IT.
你这么说有什么根据吗?
AND WHAT DO YOU BASE THIS ON?
这是整个世界的样子 没错吧?
LOOK, THIS IS THE WORLD, RIGHT?
可如果这块土地是一个
BUT NOW THINK OF THE WORLD...AS
有生命的物体
A LIVING BEING.
如果它有着自己的意识的话
IF IT WERE SOMEHOW CONSCIOUS,
它将会会对我们的行为 作出回应的！
THEN IT WOULD ULTIMATELY BECOME AWARE OF OUR AFFECT ON IT.
这片土地是有意识的...
RIGHT, THE WORLD IS CONSCIOUS --
这是我听过最冷的笑话了...
IT MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
哈罗 有人吗？
HELLO?  ANYBODY?
如果我们继续过度开发的话
IF WE HAVE MADE TOO MUCH OF AN IMPACT,
也许我们会全部灭亡的
THEN THAT CONSCIOUSNESS WOULD TRY TO SNUFF US OUT.
我觉得我们正在面临着一场
I THINK WE'RE LOOKING AT A GLOBAL CATASTROPHE,
前所未有的大灾难
THE LIKES OF WHICH WE'VE NEVER SEEN.
谁他妈相信你呀？
POO DIGGERY AND POPPY COCK.
我想我们最好把所有虱子都集中起来
I THINK WE NEED TO PUT ALL RESOURCES
大家一起商量探讨一下
NOW INTO A FULL INVESTIGATION,
关于大迁移的可能性
PERHAPS EVEN BEGIN A LICE-WIDE EVACUATION.
大迁移?
EVACUATION?
可是明天是庆生节呀!
TOMORROW IS THE GOOTAK FESTIVAL!
你知道这会造成多大的损失吗?
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH MONEY WE WOULD LOSE?
以后不要再乱造谣了
ESCORT MR. MAYFIELD OUT,
总统是不会理会你这种 哗众取宠的小把戏的
THE PRESIDENT CAN'T BE BOTHERED ANY FURTHER.
副总统 Greg 你这贱人
DAMN YOU, VICE PRESIDENT GREG,
你会成为千古罪人的
YOU COULD BE KILLING US ALL.
这实在是...
THIS IS SO
太丢脸了
EMBARRASSING.
我是来检查听力的
I HAVE AN EAR INFECTION.
你是因为什么缘故要来看医生?
WHAT ARE YOU SEEING THE DOCTOR FOR?
我得了...
I HAVE...
我得了AIDS.
I HAVE AIDS.
Clyde Harris?
CLYDE HARRIS?
哇 看来你的头虱问题真的很严重呢
YEAH, THAT'S A PRETTY BAD LICE PROBLEM THERE,
你们学校的检查还真是及时呢
GOOD THING THEY PULLED YOU OUT OF SCHOOL.
可为什么是我呀 医生?
BUT WHY ME, DOCTOR?
为什么是我?
WHY ME?
我怎么会染上这种东西?!
HOW DID I GET THIS?!
恩 信不信由你哦
WELL, BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
有些虱子会主动停附在苍蝇身上
SOME LICE CAN ACTUALLY ATTACH THEMSELVES TO FLIES
直到苍蝇带他们飞到
AND THEN WAIT FOR THE FLY TO LAND ON SOMEONE'S HEAD
一个适合于他们产卵的地方
WHERE THEY CAN REPRODUCE.
所以说你的这些虱子
AND THEN THE LICE THAT LIVE IN YOUR HEAD
估计都是你头上土生土长的呢
NOW WERE PROBABLY ALL BORN THERE.
恶心...
SICK.
这瓶香波可以解决问题
THIS SHAMPOO SHOULD TAKE CARE OF IT.
洗澡的时候用上就好了
USE THIS IN THE SHOWER --
你的头皮可能会有一些灼痛感
YOUR SCALP MAY BURN A BIT AFTERWARDS,
但它能把那些虱子 一个不留地全部干掉
BUT IT SHOULD KILL... EVERY LAST ONE OF THEM.
Travis?
TRAVIS?
你还好吧?
EVERYTHING OKAY?
Kelly...
KELLY...
我只是在担心我们的宝宝
I WAS JUST THINKING ABOUT OUR BABY.
我想给她起名叫
I WANT TO NAME HER
希望
HOPE.
希望?
HOPE?
为了明天生存的希望...
HOPE FOR A CHANCE AT TOMORROW.
怎么忽然开始下雨了？
IT'S RAINING? NOW?
我喜欢雨！
I LOVE THE RAIN!
噢 上帝啊
OH, MY GOD.
我们得马上离开这里!
WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE!
什么?
WHAT?
只不过是下雨而已嘛
IT'S JUST RAIN.
我们得马上离开 Kelly!
WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE NOW, KELLY!
这是什么?
WHAT IS THAT?
大家快爬到树上去!!
EVERYONE GET UP INTO THE TREES!!
爬得越高越好!!
WE HAVE TO GET UP HIGH!!
坚持住呀 Kelly!
COME ON, KELLY!
上帝啊!
MY GOD!
Travis 他们全都挂了!
TRAVIS, THEY'RE ALL DYING!
别往下看Kelly.
DON'T LOOK, KELLY.
别往下看
DON'T LOOK.
这他妈到底是什么!
WHAT THE HELL IS IIIIIITTTTT!
好啦 现在终于安全了
IT'S OKAY-- WE'RE SAFE UP HERE.
我怎么有不祥的预感...
I DON'T THINK SO.
Travis!!!
TRAVIS!!!
Kelly!!!
KELLY!!!
坚持住!!!
HANG ON!!!
我坚持不下去了!!
I CAN'T HANG ON!!
你必须坚持!!
YOU HAVE TO!!
为了孩子!!
FOR THE BABY!!
Kelly....!!!!
KELLYYYYYY!!!!
不要啊!!
NO!!
不...要...啊...!!!!!!
NOOOOOOOOO!!!!!!
好啦 孩子们
OKAY, KIDS,
今天我们还是来学习一下内战的历史.
TODAY WE'RE GOING TO REVIEW SOME CIVIL WAR HISTORY.
谁能告诉我内战是什么时候开始的？.
-WHO CAN TELL ME WHAT YEAR THE WAR STARTED? -WAIT, WAIT.
哇... 哇...哇 那件事最后怎么样了?
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA... SO WHAT HAPPENED?
什么事?
WITH WHAT?
虱子检查呀!
WITH THE LICE EXAM!
他们发现有人有虱子了吗?!
DID THEY FIND ANYBODY WITH LICE?!
恩 他们的确发现了一些人有虱子
YES -- SOME LICE WAS DISCOVERED
但问题都已经解决了
AND THE PROPER ACTION HAS BEEN TAKEN.
我们班有人有虱子不?
SOMEBODY IN THIS CLASS?
恩...有的
UH...YES.
是谁有虱子呀?
WELL, WHO WAS IT?
是Kenny吗?!
IT WAS KENNY, RIGHT?!
现在追究有什么意义呢?
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
这件事已经结束了
IT'S OVER.
没有意义?
DOESN'T MATTER?
我们有知道 到底是谁有头虱的权利!
IF SOMEBODY HAD PARASITES IN THEIR HAIR,WE NEED TO KNOW WHO!
快说吧 到底是不是Kenny?
IT WAS KENNY, WASN'T IT?
我也想知道到底是谁有虱子!
I WANNA KNOW WHO IT  WAS, TOO!
这可不能告诉你们
IT'S BEING KEPT CONFIDENTIAL.
学校里面有政策
THERE'S A POLICY IN THE SCHOOLS
要保护长头虱学生的隐私权
NOT TO SINGLE OUT A KID WHO HAS LICE
不然他们将会被你们这些贱人 折磨到崩溃的
BECAUSE OF THE EMBARRASSMENT IT CAN CAUSE,
清楚了吗?
OKAY?
真他妈胡说八道!
THAT IS BULLCRAP!
这个举动限制了我们作为小孩
YOU ARE DENYING OUR RIGHTS AS CHILDREN
侮辱 欺负 鄙视 嘲笑 恶心
TO TOTALLY RIP ON THAT KID
那个长头虱的孩子的权利
AND MAKE HIM OR HER FEEL LIKE AN OUTCAST.
没错!
YEAH!
我们有权利知道
AND WE HAVE A RIGHT TO KNOW
到底是哪个男孩子有头虱
WHICH BOY HAD LICE IN HIS HAIR
这样我们才能决定不和他约会!
SO WE DON'T EVER GO OUT WITH THEM!
你又怎么知道是男孩子有头虱?!
HOW DO WE KNOW IT WAS A BOY?!
也很可能是你们这些臭女生的 其中一个有头虱呀
IT COULD JUST HAVE EASILY BEEN ONE OF YOU STUPID GIRLS!
没错!
YEAH!
打倒女生!
DUMB GIRLS!
这件事已经完结了
THE CASE IS CLOSED.
不管那些虱子长在谁头上 它们都已经挂了
WHOEVER HAD THE LICE, THEY'RE DEAD NOW.
我们还是来接着学习内战的历史吧
WE'RE MOVING ON TO CIVIL WAR HISTORY.
希望..希望..你还活着..
HOPE -- HOPE, YOU'RE ALIVE.
天啊
MY GOD.
救救我
HELP ME.
救救我...
HELP MEEEEEEE.
Travis!
TRAVIS!
在这呢!
OVER HERE!
Travis如果不是你告诉我们 要赶快爬到树上去,
TRAVIS, IF YOU HADN'T WARNED US TO GET UP IN THE TREES,
我们早就全部都挂了.
WE WOULD ALL BE DEAD.
有多少位幸存者?
HOW MANY SURVIVORS?
我们六个人和..
JUST THE SIX OF US --
副总统.
AND THE VICE PRESIDENT.
你这个臭婊子养的!
YOU SON OF A BITCH-- !
你本来可以阻止这一切发生的!!!
YOU HAD A CHANCE TO STOP THIS!!!
如果我们能够熬过这次难关
SO HELP ME, IF WE LIVE THROUGH THIS
我一定要把你关进监狱!
I AM GOING TO SEE YOU ROT IN PRISON!
我们现在该怎么办?
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
这场大灾难还没结束呢
WE AREN'T OUT OF THIS YET.
你们两个 再去搜索一下还有没有幸存者
YOU TWO, LOOK FOR OTHER SURVIVORS.
你们尽可能地去搜集食物 把它们全部带到这里
YOU GET WHATEVER FOOD YOU CAN AND BRING IT BACK HERE.
谁给你命令大家的权利的?
WHO PUT YOU IN CHARGE?
是主赋予我的
GOD DID,
在他杀我妻子的时候...
WHEN HE KILLED MY WIFE.
好啦 长虱子的那个人
ALRIGHT, THE PERSON WHO HAD HEAD LICE
赶快出来坦白吧
NEEDS TO SPEAK UP RIGHT NOW,
好让我们从此以后不和你接触!
SO THAT WE KNOW TO STAY AWAY FROM YOU!
对 站出来!
YEAH, COME ON!
我们迟早都会把你抓出来的!
WE'RE GONNA FIND OUT SOONER OR LATER!
不管你是谁
OKAY, WHOEVER YOU ARE,
你不止是个头虱男! 你还是个撒谎男!
YOU ARE NOW NOT ONLY A LICE HEAD, YOU ARE A LIAR!
你这样做只会使大家蒙羞!
YOU'RE ONLY MAKING THIS WORSE ON YOURSELF!
你猜怎么着...
YOU KNOW WHAT...
我觉得的你就是头虱男!
I'LL BET IT WAS YOU!
就证明了你自己有头虱!
IF THEY FOUND LICE IN YOUR HAIR!
带领大家一起对抗 一个假想的头虱男
TRY TO LEAD THE CHARGE AGAINST SOMEBODY ELSE
从而为你自己洗清嫌疑!
TO TAKE THE SUSPICION OFF OF YOURSELF!
我不这么认为哦 Stan!
I DON'T THINK SO, KYLE!
可你知道吗..
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT..
你现在的反应
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT YOU WOULD DO
就证明了你才是头虱男
IF YOU HAD HAD HEAD LICE.
带领大家把矛头对准我...
TRY TO GET EVERYONE TO BLAME ME.
你们两个别吵了
YOU GUYS STOP IT,
吵架不能给我们带来任何帮助...
THIS ISN'T GETTING US ANYWHERE.
你现在的反应
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT YOU WOULD DO
证明了你才是头虱男 Stan.
IF YOU HAD HAD HEAD LICE, STAN.
没错 出来扮演和事佬的角色
YEAH, TRY TO HAVE EVERYONE MAKE PEACE
从而想把这件事 大事化小 小事化了
SO IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE A BIG DEAL.
而Kenny的表现也证明了 他自己是头虱男 --
AND THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT KENNY WOULD DO --
站在那却一句话也不说..
STAND HERE AND SAY NOTHING.
那如果我有虱子的话 我的反应会是什么样呢?!
HEY GUYS, WHAT WOULD I DO?!
我们不如去找个放大镜来
LET'S JUST GET A MAGNIFYING GLASS
把所有人的头发都好好看上一遍
AND LOOK AT EVERYONE'S HEADS!
现在太迟了 --
IT'S TOO LATE --
那些虱子应该都被医生给杀掉了
THE TREATMENT WOULD HAVE KILLED IT ALL.
根本就没有办法嘛
THERE'S NO WAY TO TELL.
办法肯定是有的
THERE'S A WAY.
肯定会有一个 找出那个傻逼头虱男的办法
THERE'S A WAY TO FIND OUT WHO HAD SICK ASS HEAD COOTIES,AND I'M GONNA FIND IT.
是他...
IT WAS HIM...
头虱男绝对是他!
IT HAD TO HAVE BEEN HIM.
没错,..
YEAH...
可你也有嫌疑...
OR YOU.
Mark?!?!
MARK?!?!
Mark  你要坚持住!
MARK, YOU HAVE TO HANG ON!
这一切还远远没有结束呢
THIS ISN'T GOING TO STOP.
这块土地正在排斥我们
THE WORLD IS REJECTING US.
如果我们想要继续繁衍种族 我们得离开这个星球
IF WE'RE GOING TO LIVE, WE HAVE TO GET OFF THIS PLANET.
怎么做?
HOW?
首先 我们得穿越森林
FIRST, WE HAVE TO GO OUT OF THE FOREST
进入荒漠大禁区
INTO THE FORBIDDEN ZONE.
这是唯一可能行得通的 离开这个星球的办法了
IT'S THE ONLY WAY WE MIGHT EVEN SEE ANOTHER PLANET.
荒漠大禁区?
THE FORBIDDEN ZONE?
我们会全部暴露在阳光下
WE'LL BE EXPOSED --
我们会在那挂掉的..
WE'LL DIE OUT THERE.
我们会在这挂掉的!
WE'LL DIE HERE.
这个星球正试着毁灭我们
LOOK, THE WORLD IS GETTING RID OF US,
你们难道还没发现吗!?
DON'T YOU GET IT!?
毁灭我们?
GETTING RID OF US,
你的意思是它是在有意识的活动?
YOU MEAN LIKE IT KNOWS WHAT IT'S DOING?
没错!
YES!
因为我们不记后果的过分开采!
BECAUSE MAYBE WE ROLLED THE DICE TOO MANY TIMES!
我是不会离开我丈夫的
I'M NOT LEAVING MY HUSBAND.
没错 我觉得这片土地还有希望
YEAH, I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES HERE.
你们爱怎么着我不管.
YOU CAN ALL STAY HERE.
可我要保护我的孩子
I'M GOING TO TRY TO SAVE MY BABY.
我和你一起去
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
这地方已经没有什么东西值得我留念了
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT FOR ME HERE.
我也想和你一起...
I WANT TO GO, TOO.
去你妈的
NOT A CHANCE.
我承认我原来错了...好吗
LOOK, I KNOW I MESSED UP, ALRIGHT?!
可我现在已经醒悟了呀
BUT I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
如果我们离开这片森林
IF WE CAN GET OUT OF THE FOREST,
我们也许能找到一片新的乐土
WE MIGHT FIND ANOTHER PLACE TO LIVE!
如果我们找到了出路的话
IF WE FIND ANYTHING,
我们会回来接应大家的
WE'LL TRY TO SEND HELP FOR THE REST OF YOU.
上路吧
LET'S GO.
你到底走不走呀 副总统
COME ON IF YOU'RE COMING, MR. VICE PRESIDENT.
YEAH...
马上就来
RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
好啦 把门关上吧
ALRIGHT, LOCK THAT DOOR, CRAIG.
这是干嘛呀Cartman?
WHAT'S THIS ABOUT, CARTMAN?
我已经想到办法了
I'VE COME UP WITH A TEST THAT CAN DETERMINE
一个可以找出头虱男的办法
IF IT WAS ANY OF US WHO HAD THE HEAD LICE.
我们将在今天把所有问题一次性解决.
WE'RE GONNA FIND OUT ONCE AND FOR ALL WHO HAD HEAD COOTIES.
虱子和蚊子一样 都是要吸取人血的
LICE FEED ON A PERSON'S BLOOD. AND JUST LIKE MOSQUITOES,
他们会在它的寄主的血中
THEY LEAVE BEHIND SMALL TRACES OF THEIR SALIVA
留下一点点唾液
IN THE HOST'S BLOODSTREAM.
而这些唾液有个很奇怪的特点
AND THAT SALIVA IS MOLOCROMAGNIC.
如果用一根烧红的铁丝 去接触被感染过的血
SO IF AN INFECTED PERSON'S BLOOD IS TOUCHED BY A HOT METAL COIL,
被感染过的血将会...
SAY, THAT PERSON'S BLOOD...
在空中溅起10米高...
WILL JUMP TEN METERS INTO THE AIR.
真..真..真...真的吗?
R-R-R-REALLY?
什么破鸡巴玩意啊!
THAT'S RETARDED!
这个实验根本就不是你想出来的 Cartman
YOU DIDN'T COME UP WITH THAT EXPERIMENT, CARTMAN,
你只不过是看了”怪型”那部电影罢了
YOU SAW IT IN THAT MOVIE 'THE THING'!
这个科学测试的目的是...
THIS IS A SCIENTIFIC TEST DESIGNED TO --
你只不过是照搬电影情节而已 你在浪费大家的时间!
YOU SAW IT IN 'THE THING' AND YOU'RE WASTING EVERYONE'S TIME!
我就知道你会这么说 Kyle.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT SAY THAT, KYLE.
因为你害怕这个测试 我没说错吧?!
BECAUSE YOU DON'T WANT TO TAKE THE TEST, DO YOU?!
不管有没有感染虱子 人的血都不会溅起来的!
NOBODY'S BLOOD IS GOING TO JUMP UP IN THE AIR!
如果这个实验是假的 那你到底在害怕什么呢?!
IF IT DOESN'T WORK, THEN WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF?!
只有一种人才会害怕这个实验
THE ONLY PERSON WHO WOULDN'T WANT TO TAKE THE TEST IS
那些害怕这个实验 会把他们的小秘密全部无情揭穿的
SOMEBODY WHO WAS WORRIED IT MIGHT WORK
傻逼头虱男!
AND REVEAL THAT THEY WERE THE ONES WITH LICE!
YEAH...
说得没错!
THAT'S TRUE.
我才不怕什么测试呢
I HAVE NO PROBLEM TAKING THE TEST.
我根本就没有秘...秘...秘...秘密
I HAVE NOTHING TO H-H-H-HIDE.
我也没有秘密
YEAH, ME NEITHER.
好吧 好吧 我参加这个傻逼测试就是了
ALRIGHT, FINE, I'LL DO THE DUMB TEST!
每人都领好一个培养皿和一个注射器
EVERYONE TAKE A PETRI DISH AND A SYRINGE.
抽30毫升的血放进培养皿...
WE NEED AT LEAST 30 CCS OF BLOOD FROM EACH OF YOU.
好啦 现在请大家回原位做好
ALRIGHT, NOW EVERYONE BACK OVER THERE...
大不了先从我开始好了
WE'LL START WITH WHAT I ALREADY KNOW.
哇 看来Kyle真的不是头虱男呢
OH, GUESS THAT PROVES ERIC WASN'T THE ONE WITH HEAD LICE!
这根本就不能证明什么!
IT DOESN'T PROVE ANYTHING!
是吗 那我们就来看看你的血样 是什么反应吧 Kyle....?
YEAH? LET'S JUST SEE WHAT YOUR BLOOD DOES, KYLE....?
恩..看来你也是干净的呀
HUH... I GUESS YOU'RE CLEAN.
伙计们  我们得回去上课啦
YOU GUYS, WE BETTER GO, RECESS IS ALMOST OVER.
没事 很快就结束了
ALRIGHT, WON'T TAKE MUCH LONGER
我操?!
WHAT THE HELL?!
Kenny!!!
KENNY!!!
这..怎么可能?
NO WAY.
真的被你说中了呀  Eric!
YOU WERE RIGHT ALL ALONG, ERIC!
真的是Kenny!
IT WAS KENNY!
那当然啦!
OF COURSE I WAS RIGHT!
我早说过了嘛! 只有穷人才会得虱子!
I TOLD YOU ONLY POOR PEOPLE GET LICE!
我们成功了!
WE'VE DONE IT!
我们终于来到荒漠大禁区了!
WE'VE REACHED THE FORBIDDEN ZONE!
我从小就听过有关这地方的传说
I'VE ALWAYS HEARD STORIES ABOUT THIS PLACE.
可没想到它居然是真实的存在
NEVER THOUGHT IT WAS REAL.
它当然是真的啦...
IT'S REAL...
就好象我对我孩子的爱一样真
REAL AS MY LOVE FOR MY UNBORN BABY.
你的计划到底是什么呢Travis?
SO WHAT IS EXACTLY IS YOUR PLAN, TRAVIS?
我们的先祖就是从外面的世界来到这儿的
OUR ANCESTORS CAME HERE FROM ANOTHER WORLD.
也许在这以外还存在着其他的世界
MAYBE THERE'S STILL OTHER WORLDS OUT THERE
有着象我们一样的生命体
WITH LIFE FORMS LIKE US.
也许在那些世界里面
MAYBE THERE'S EVEN A WORLD
那些生命体与他们的星球
WHERE THEY'VE LEARNED TO LIVE WITH THE PLANET
和平共处 相糯以沫 共同构建着和谐社会..
INSTEAD OF JUST ON IT.
Travis...
TRAVIS...
Travis... 你是如此聪明 如此强壮
TRAVIS... YOU'RE SO WISE... SO STRONG...
如果我们能够度过这次难关...
IF WE MAKE IT OUT OF THIS...
我希望能...
I'D LIKE TO...
与你携手一生..
BE WITH YOU?
对不起 女士
SORRY, BABE.
但在我的心上
BUT MY HEART IS FOREVER STENCILED
永远都只会有一个名字
IN PERMANENT INK WITH THE NAME
'Kelly'.
'KELLY'.
她能得到你这样的男虱 真是一生之幸
SHE WAS A LUCKY WOMAN TO HAVE YOU.
这和幸运没有关系
LUCK HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
对不起哦 打扰你们两个的蜜月了
SORRY TO CUT THE HONEYMOON SHORT.
你这样做是为什么? 混蛋谋杀犯!
WHY, YOU MURDERING BASTARD!
你那些关于另外一个世界的假说 就在这里终结吧
YOUR LITTLE FANTASY OF ANOTHER WORLD ENDS HERE.
快走
WALK.
你他妈到底要干什么? 副总统?
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT, VICE PRESIDENT?
快走!!!!
WALK!!!!
Clyde 快去公园!
CLYDE, DUDE, GET DOWN TO THE PARK!
我们抓住Kenny了 而他会受到惩罚的!
WE CAUGHT KENNY AND WE'RE ALL GONNA LET HIM HAVE IT!
他对我们所有人撒了谎
HE LIED TO US ALL.
他背叛了他们头虱穷人的尊严
HE BETRAYED HIS KIND.
所以他将受到最严厉的惩罚
WE ALL KNOW WHAT HAS TO HAPPEN.
准备好一只臭袜子和一块肥皂
GRAB A SOCK AND A BAR OF SOAP
一会公园见!!
AND MEET US AT THE PARK!!
伙计们...等等...
YOU GUYS...WAIT...
怎么啦  Clyde.
WHAT, CLYDE.
我...
I...
没事了...
NOTHING.
那就好 一会见咯!
ALRIGHT! SEE YOU THERE!
要记住拿臭袜子和肥皂!
REMEMBER, A BAR OF SOAP AND A SOCK!
Kenny罪该万死!
KENNY'S GONNA GET IT!
没错!
YEAH!
嗨
YELLO.
MS. GARRISON... 你的一个学生
MS. GARRISON... ONE OF YOUR STUDENTS
正在公园里被其他孩子暴打...
IS ABOUT TO BE ATTACKED AT THE PARK BY THE OTHER STUDENTS.
你是谁呀?
WHO IS THIS?
求求你了 快去公园吧!
PLEASE, JUST HURRY TO THE PARK!
你必须得阻止他们!
YOU HAVE TO STOP THEM!
非常好
THAT'S GOOD.
这就够远了
THAT'S FAR ENOUGH.
你到底要干什么?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
我要回到村子里去
I'M GOING TO GO BACK TO THE VILLAGE.
领导重建工作
START TO REBUILD.
与所有的女性交配
MATE WITH THE FEMALES.
成为...
BECOME...
总统
PRESIDENT.
你还不明白吗 这个星球在试着把我们赶出去
DON'T YOU GET IT-- THE WORLD DOESN'T WANT YOU HERE.
不到我们全部灭亡它是不会停止的!
IT'S NOT GOING TO STOP UNTIL YOU'RE DEAD!
这只不过是场灾难而已
IT WAS A DISASTER.
灾难总会发生的
DISASTERS HAPPEN.
你就死在这里好啦
THEN GO AHEAD AND DIE THERE.
我要带着我的孩子离开
I'M LEAVING WITH MY BABY.
实际上你哪里都去不了啦 Travis.
ACTUALLY, YOU'RE NEVER LEAVING HERE EITHER, TRAVIS.
干死你!!! 为什么要这样!?!?
DAMN YOU!!! WHY!?!?
因为我成为总统以后 是不能容忍你这样的虫子的
BECAUSE WHEN I'M PRESIDENT I CAN'T HAVE PESTS LIKE YOU
一直在散步着这个星球是生命体的谣言
CONSTANTLY TRYING TO PREACH THAT THE WORLD IS ALIVE.
你这个杞人忧天的傻逼
YOU'RE AN IDEALISTIC FOOL!
这个星球是不会有意识的
THE WORLD IS NOT CONSCIOUS.
我们才是有意识的!
WE ARE CONSCIOUS!
如果这星球有生命的话 它会感受到这个的!!!
IF THE WORLD WAS ALIVE, IT WOULD FEEL THIS!!!
噢
OW.
给我受死吧
YOU DIE HERE.
Kenny Mckormick,
KENNY MCKORMICK,
你被指控在学校传染虱子
YOU ARE CHARGED WITH BRINGING HEAD COOTIES INTO OUR SCHOOL
并且一直向大家隐瞒事实真相
AND LYING ABOUT IT TO COVER YOUR ASS.
你认罪吗?!
HOW DO YOU PLEAD?!
无罪!
NOT GUILTY!
有罪！我说了算!!!
GUILTY! I THOUGHT SO!!!
好啦！大家开始吧!
ALRIGHT, LET'S DO THIS!
伙计们 或许我们应该再等这么几分钟
YOU GUYS, MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST WAIT A FEW MORE MINUTES... (WHERE IS HE...?)
好啦 Kenny.
ALRIGHT, KENNY.
你知道你将受到什么惩罚吗...
YOU KNOW WHAT HAS TO HAPPEN...
臭袜皂杀!!!
SOCK BATH!!!
大家先用肥皂帮他刷牙 再用臭袜子帮他擦干净！
EVERYONE WASH KENNY WITH THE SOAP AND DRY HIM OFF WITH THE SOCKS!
NO, NO!! NOT THE SOCKS!!
WAIT... WAIT!!
快停下 快停下！
WAIT. STOP IT! STOP IT!!!
我不能看到Kenny受到这样的折磨
I CAN'T LET KENNY BE SOCK DRIED.
可他就是头虱男 而且他还撒谎了呀!!
HE HAD COOTIES AND HE LIED ABOUT IT!!
Kenny才不是头虱男呢！
KENNY DIDN'T HAVE THE HEAD LICE, ALRIGHT?!?!!!!
我才是头虱男
IT WAS ME.
什么?
WHAT?
我才是头虱男
I WAS THE ONE.
我太害怕了 以至于不敢说出真相
I WAS TOO AFRAID TO SAY ANYTHING.
但我不能让Kenny替我受罚
BUT I CAN'T LET KENNY BE SOCK DRIED FOR IT.
你到底在扯些什么呀 Kyle?
WHY ARE YOU SAYING THAT, KYLE?
你才不是头虱男呢
YOU CAN'T BE THE ONE WHO HAD HEAD LICE.
因为我才是
BECAUSE I WAS.
YOU'RE JUST TRYING TO MAKE ME FEEL BAD
BECAUSE YOU FIGURED THAT OUT, DIDN'T YOU?
什...么...?
WAIT A MINUTE... WHAT?
噢 我知道了
OH, I GET IT--
看来这是针对我的超级恶作剧啊
THIS IS SOME KIND OF BIG TRICK ON ME.
你们都知道我才是真正的头虱男了 是吧？
YOU'VE KNOWN I WAS THE ONE WITH HEAD LICE ALL ALONG, HUH?!
你也有头虱?!
YOU HAD HEAD LICE?!
当然啦!
OF COURSE!
要不然的话我怎么会 费尽苦心设计那个试验
WHY DO YOU THINK I WENT THROUGH
好把责任全部转移到Kenny身上
THAT ELABORATE BULLCRAP EXPERIMENT TO FRAME KENNY.
全部都有头虱
YOU ALL HAD HEAD LICE.
班上的每一个人
EVERY SINGLE PERSON IN THE CLASS.
不管是男生还是女生
THE BOYS AND THE GIRLS.
虱子传播的速度超快的！ 你们这帮小屁孩！
LICE SPREADS FAST, YOU DUMBASSES.
我还以为我是唯一一个头虱男呢!
I THOUGHT I WAS THE ONLY ONE!
我也是...
ME, TOO.
可这就是说 --
BUT THAT MEANS --
Kenny的确是撒了慌!
THAT MEANS KENNY WAS LYING!
臭袜皂杀!!
SOCK BATH!!
-SOCK BATH!! -YEAH.
Kelly... Kelly, 你能听见我的声音吗?
KELLY... KELLY, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
我不知道你能否听见
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAN
但我还是希望你知道
BUT...I WANT YOU TO KNOW
我已经 我已经保护不了我们的孩子了
I TRIED... I TRIED TO SAVE OUR BABY...
我让你失望了 宝贝
BUT I LET YOU DOWN, BABE.
K... Kelly...?
K... KELLY...?
欢迎来到新世界
YOU ARE WELCOME HERE.
你现在安全了...
YOU'RE SAFE NOW...
我们在这里已经幸福和谐地
WE HAVE LIVED HERE FOR GENERATION AFTER GENERATION.
生活了好几代了
NEVER BEING DISTURBED.
我们成功了 希望！
WE MADE IT, HOPE.
我们成功了！ Kelly!!!
WE MADE IT, KELLY!!!
先生们 女士们 有请ANGELINA JOLIE!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, MISS ANGELINA JOLIE!!
哈罗 大家好呀
HELLO, EVERYONE!
哈罗！
HELLO!!